刚刚真是
That was...
前十  至少
Top ten, at least.
也许是前二十
Ma- maybe top 20.
没到前十吗
Not top ten?
前十里有巴黎那次
There was Paris.
瓜拉
Kualai.
洋基棒球场
Yankee stadium.
-波克洛山上那个地方  -是的
- Oh, that place in the Poconos. - Yes.
米克诺斯群岛
Mykonos.
科尼岛
Coney island.
然后还有斯塔恩岛
And then there was Staten island.
差点忘了热气球里那次
Oh, and the hot air balloon.
还有西敏寺狗展  那次真棒
The Westminster dog show. That was...
这样也只有九次
That's only nine.
你怀上了阿丽克西斯的那晚
Well, the night we made Alexis.
我们那会儿很开心  不是么
We have had fun, haven’t we?
让人怀疑我们为什么要离婚
Makes you wonder why we ever got divorced.
我也觉得
I know, right?
要不是你和你的导演有了外遇
I mean, except for you having an affair with your director
然后搬到了马里布
And moving to Malibu
给了我离婚协议书
And serving me with divorce papers,
我觉得我们还是有机会的
I think we really had a chance.
我要搬回来
I'm moving back.
搬回纽约吗
Back to new York?
我太想念这儿了
I miss it.
我想念纽约  我想阿丽克西斯  我想你
I miss it. I miss Alexis. I miss you.
那你的工作怎么办
Uh, what about your career?
洛杉矶物是人非了
Oh, L.A.'S changed.
像我这种程度的演员找不到
Uh, the juicy roles just aren't there
报酬丰厚的角色
For an actress of my caliber.
我需要改变  或许可以去百老汇试试
I need a change, like Broadway maybe.
-话剧舞台  -是的  但
- The legitimate stage. - Yeah, but-
暂停
Time- out, hey.
梅瑞狄斯  等等
Meredith, hold on
你真的仔细考虑过吗
Have you really thought this through?
还要考虑什么
What's to think about?
你  我  和阿丽克西斯
You, me, Alexis-
住在同一个城市里
All living in the same city-
不就跟以前一样了么
It's gonna be just like old times.
灵书妙探
第一季第六集
死者是非洲裔美国男性
Vic's an African- American male,
二十出头
Early 20s.
多处刺伤
Multiple stab wounds,
手臂和躯干上有多处挫伤
Contusions on the arms and torso.
尸体被一个流浪汉发现
The body was discovered by a homeless guy.
死前被殴打  有可能遭受折磨
He was beaten, maybe tortured.
看起来像某种仪式杀人
Looks like some kind of ritualistic killing.
你觉得呢
You think?
你还好吧
You okay?
今早我和我前妻上床了
I had sex with my ex-wife this morning.
我的第一任妻子  梅瑞狄斯
My first ex-wife-Meredith-
也就是阿丽克西斯的母亲
Alexis' mom.
她在考虑搬回纽约住
And she's thinking  About moving back to New York.
你知道那对我意味着什么吗
Do you know what that would mean to me?
那将会是一种非常特别的地狱
That would be a very special brand of hell-
煎熬并快乐着
The hell of a deep-fried twinkie.
A deep-fried twinkie?
是的  那种罪恶的快感
Yeah, the guilty pleasure
你知道对你自己没好处
That you know is bad for you,
所以你出于新奇
So you only do it once
一年会来上一两次
Maybe twice a year for the novelty.
但每天都煎熬并快乐着真是
But a deep-fried twinkie every day is-
卡塞尔
Castle!
犯罪现场  死尸  缺少应有的尊重
Crime scene. Dead body. Little respect here.
我想尸体听不到我说话
I don't think he can hear me.
好  那你多一点自尊总行吧
Okay, how about a little self-respect then?
算了  检查一下他的口腔
Fine. Check out his mouth.
里面可能会有一个小袋子
There's probably a little pouch in there.
-你怎么知道的  -打开
- How did you know? - Open it.
这是什么意思
What does it mean?
-是伏都教  -伏都教
- It's vodun.  - Vodun?
是不是《星际迷航》一类的玩意儿
What, is that some kind of "Star Trek" thing?
不是  老兄  是一种宗教
No, dude, it's a religion,
主要在非洲西部流行
Practiced primarily in west Africa.
看什么  我也读书的
What? I read, too.
碗里的血
The, uh, blood in the bowl-
很可能是动物血
Most likely animal.
是仪式的一部分
Part of the ceremony.
小袋子是对圣灵的供奉
The pouch is an offering to the spirits,
但是我无法辨认那个符号
But I don't recognize the symbol.
如果你认出来了  你就是嫌疑犯
Well, if you did, you'd be a suspect.
你是怎么知道这些东西的
So how do you know about all this?
为德里克·斯道姆系列第六本做的调查
Research for my sixth Derrick Storm novel.
-《邪恶风暴》  -没错  多谢
- "Unholy Storm."  - Yes, thank you.
还有  伏都教并不仅限于西非
And, uh, vodun's not just limited to west Africa.
海地人也有信奉它的
It's also practiced by Haitian
还有纽约的多米尼加裔社区
And dominican communities right here in New York.
让犯罪现场勘查组检查袋子
Have C.S.U. run the pouch.
让法医检查血液
Have an M.E. Test the blood.
在系统里查查指纹
And let's get his fingerprints in the system,
看看有没有对应的
See if there's an I.D.
这个仪式  我猜
This ritual-I assume then
它是为了一个特殊目的而进行的
It was done for a specific purpose?
前提是你猜想
That's only if you're assuming
罪犯还是有理性的
That the guy doing this was rational.
不  她是正确的
No, no, she's right.
或许对你我来说这没有意义
It might not make sense to you or me,
但如果能找到他这么做的原因
But, uh, if we found out why he did this,
我们就可能找到凶手
We might find your killer.
我们可以说就是这么工作的
Yeah, that's kinda how we do it.
你还有那份研究报告吗
Do you still have the research?
事实上  我留着呢
As a matter of fact, I do.
"这个仪式的目的
"The purpose of their rituals
"是想与圣灵和圣灵界沟通
"Was to make contact with the spirits and the spirit world,
"通过祭祀来博得他们的喜爱
"To gain their favor through sacrifice.
"斯道姆很确定  他可以牺牲一切
"Storm was pretty sure he'd sacrifice anything
"他看着护身符有节奏地
"When he saw the amulet swaying
"前后摇摆
"Rhythmically back and forth
在女人裸露而有光泽的两峰之间"
Between the woman's bare, glistening breasts."
《邪恶风暴》
"Unholy storm"?
你把我拖到这里
You dragged me in here
就是为了读你的破书
So that you could read from your own book?
这书里有很多好东西
Hey, there's a lot of good stuff in here,
其中的一部分是很真实的
And some of it is factual.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
我还有一个谋杀案要解决
I have a murder to solve.
我以为我们就是在解决那个
I thought that's what we were doing.
好吧  我只是  开玩笑
Okay, look, I'm so-I-I am just kidding.
我还有一份资料
I do have another source.
你居然说你的前妻让你煎熬并快乐着
And you call your ex-wife a "deep-fried twinkie."
相信我  你都觉得我讨厌又烦人
Oh, trust me-as annoying and intrusive you think I am,
她比我糟糕一百万倍
She is a million times worse.
你考虑过阿丽克西斯吗
What about Alexis?
也许她很想念母亲
Maybe she misses her mom.
也许让她回来是个好主意
Maybe it would be a good idea to have her back in town.
有一次  阿丽克西斯九岁的时候
This once, when Alexis was 9,
梅瑞狄斯顺路接她去吃午饭
Meredith dropped by to take her out to lunch.
-然后呢  -去巴黎吃午饭  巴黎
- So?  - In Paris. Paris!
然后她又表现得跟个没事人似的
And then she acted like there was nothing wrong.
她是瘾君子玛咪姑妈
She's Auntie Mame on meth.
她要是真有那么坏那你今早干嘛还跟她睡
If she's so bad,Then why'd you sleep with her this morning?
让我告诉你什么叫疯子
Let me tell you something about crazy people.
今早爽得简直是不可思议
The sex is unbelievable.
你到底有多肤浅
How shallow are you?
非常  肤浅
Very.
我没时间跟你来这套
You know, I don't have time for this.
有人叫了午餐吗
Someone order lunch?
贝克特探长
Detective Beckett,
认识一下我的另一份资料
Meet my other source.
这是个伏都教的一个标志
The symbol's a vever.
代表着可以打开
A representation of one who can open
通向圣灵界的十字路口的人
Crossroads into the spirit world.
我知道的伏都教的事儿  都是米歇尔教的
Michelle taught me everything I know about vodun.
显然我教的并不多
Which obviously isn't much.
有上身裸露的姑娘和鸡血的那个场景
That scene with the topless girl and the chicken blood
那是什么玩意儿
What was that?
我有时会自由发挥
I took a few liberties.
你知道  从这个设计来看
You know, from the design,
我敢说这不是海地人所为
I'd say this isn't Haitian,
也不是牙买加人或多米尼加人
Jamaican or Dominican.
一定是尼日利亚人的中坚分子
This is hard-core Nigerian.
这个符咒是什么意思
What about this charm?
符咒是对伏都圣徒或圣灵的
The charm's an offering
一种供奉
To a vodun saint, or loa.
这里供奉的是奥贡(掌管火铁狩猎战争政治)
In this case, it's Ogun.
通常人们召唤他
He's usually called upon
来帮助寻找失物
To help find something that's been lost.
所以凶手是在寻找什么
So our killer's looking for something.
那东西可能属于被害者
Something the victim once possessed.
或许这就是他被折磨的原因
Maybe that's why he was tortured.
可以从仪式的种类
Could the kind of ceremony
看出犯人在找什么吗
Indicate what the killer was looking for?
很遗憾  不行
Unfortunately, no.
你怎么知道这么多
How do you know so much about this?
因为我是教徒
Because I practice.
大三的时候
My junior year,
我到尼日利亚留学
I spent abroad in Nigeria.
爱上了那儿的宗教和美食
Fell in love with the religion, the cuisine.
米歇尔拥有纽约最棒的尼日利亚餐馆
Michelle owns the best Nigerian restaurant in the city.
真奇怪  我绝不会把你
It's funny. I never would've pegged you
和任何神秘的事情挂钩
For the occult type.
神秘只在旁观者的眼中  探长
Occult is in the eye of the beholder, detective.
在你们看来伏都教或许很古怪
As bizarre as vodun may seem to you,
但我敢保证  西方的宗教信仰
I assure you, the beliefs of western religions
在别人眼里看来也同样古怪
Seem just as strange to outsiders.
炖牛蹄的味道怎么样
How do you like the cow's foot stew?
牛蹄
Cow's foot?
你跟我说的是牛肉
You said it was beef.
技术层面来说  牛等同于牛肉
Technically, cow is beef.
再说了  你不是挺爱吃的嘛
Besides, you liked it.
这起谋杀  也是
This murder-is, um, is that
也是仪式的一部分吗
A part of the ceremony, as well?
不是  伏都教是一种平和的
No. Vodun is a peaceful,
深入精神内部的宗教
Deeply spiritual religion
每一天  世界各地上百万的教徒
Practiced by millions of people
都在信奉它
Across the world every day.
我很怀疑凶手是否内心平和
I doubt whoever did this is very peaceful.
不
No.
犯人或许是个伏都教徒
Your killer may be vodun,
但不会因此而杀人
But that's not why this man's dead.
他被杀害
He was killed
因为他拥有
Because he had something
犯人迫切需要的东西
The killer desperately wants.
他绝不会罢手
And he's not gonna stop
直到找到他要的
Until he finds it.
抱歉
Excuse me.
我是莱恩
Yeah, it's Ryan.
又发现一名死者
We got another one.
死者叫达茜·曹
Victim's name is Darcy Cho.
在市区的一家公司当了两年律师
Second-year lawyer at a firm downtown.
多处刺伤  和上一个死者一样
Multiple stab wounds, just like the last one.
邻居发现门开着  就叫来管理员
Neighbor found the door open, called the super.
于是他们发现了死者
This is what they found.
两个现场布置完全相同
The staging is exactly the same.
是的  他们发现了以后
Yeah. When they saw what they had,
西区警局就给我们打了电话
West side boys gave us a call.
看起来她有自卫
Looks like she put up a fight.
前臂有自卫性伤口
Defensive wounds on her forearm.
现场的东西与上起案件相同
Paraphernalia is the same as the other murder.
我在她嘴里又找到了一个符咒
And I found another charm in her mouth.
犯罪现场勘查组有没有
Anything back from C.S.U.
关于上个案件的反馈
On the other scene?
蜡烛是最典型的石蜡
Candle's basic paraffin,
在任何商店都能买到
Found in any bodega.
我猜这次也一样
Figure it's gonna be the same with this one.
布是普通的红色法兰绒
The cloth is a common red flannel.
玻璃碗是中国制造的
Glass bowl-made in china.
里面的血呢
What about the blood?
是鸡血
Chicken blood.
也许她是用这个包来自卫的
Maybe she used this purse to defend herself.
他一定还没找到他要的东西
We know he hasn't found what he's looking for.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
她嘴里的符咒
The charm in her mouth.
他仍需要圣灵来引导他
He still needs the spirits to guide him.
书的第十章里
Chapter ten.
尽可能调查达茜的生平
Find out what you can about Darcy.
看看她是否认识第一个被害人
See if she knew our first victim.
我想弄清楚
I wanna know how
两起谋杀有怎样的联系
These murders are connected.
是的
Right.
西蒙斯先生  你找我吗
Mr. Simmons, you wanted to see me?
阿丽克西斯  有个坏消息要告诉你
Alexis, I’m afraid we have some bad news.
什么  不  是关于我父亲吗
What? No, is it my dad?
他是不是中枪了
Did he get shot?
亲爱的  不是你爸爸
It's not your dad, sweetie.
-老妈  -是你的外公
- Mom?  - It's your grandfather.
他今早去世了
He passed away this morning.
我外公
Grandfather?
我知道  你一时半会无法接受
I know. It's a lot to take in.
妈妈  我今天要考微积分
Mom, I have a calculus test today.
考虑到情况特殊
Given the circumstances,
布朗老师一定会让你补考的
I'm sure Mr. Brown will let you make it up.
感谢你的理解  西蒙斯先生
Thank you, Mr. Simmons, for your compassion
在这么艰难的时候
In this trying time.
走吧亲爱的  我们有很多事要做
Let's go, honey. Lots to do.
妈妈  外公六年前就去世了
Uh, mom, grandpa died six years ago.
我知道  但家里有人去世
I know, but a death in the family-
用这招儿请假  每次都很管用
Always a good excuse to get out of school.
你这招儿也太阴了吧
No, it's a creepy excuse.
不会吧  我就是想和你在一起
Come on, I need some Alexis time.
我到这儿整整一周了
Do you realize I’ve been in town a whole week,
我们都没有逛街
And we haven't even gone shopping?
我们周六一起去逛街吧
We're going shopping on Saturday...
那天我没课
When I don't have school.
但班德尔百货(走贵族路线)正在搞促销
But Bendel's is having its sale now!
我整个礼拜都在准备考试
I studied all week for this test.
好了  学数学又有什么用呢
Okay, why bother learning math
除非你打算开始实际应用
If you don't get to apply it in real-life situations,
存私房钱吗
Like calculating your savings?
别让我难过了
Come on, what's the harm?
除非你真的想回去
Unless you really want to go back
告诉西蒙斯先生  妈妈是个骗子
And tell Mr. Simmons your mother's a liar.
好吧  不过你保证不出城啊
Fine, but promise we're not leaving the city.
太好了
Come on!
不可能啊  怎么会有人对她下毒手呢
It doesn't make sense. Why would someone kill her?
布顿小姐  你的经理说
Ms. Button, your office manager
你和达茜的关系很好
Said that you and Darcy were close.
我们同时进的公司
We joined the firm at the same time.
在这儿我们人生地不熟
Neither of us knew anyone in the city,
就这样我们成为了最好的朋友
So we just, sort of, became best friends.
你认识这个男人吗
Do you recognize this man?
我们认为他和达茜有关
We think he and Darcy might be connected.
不认识
No, I don't...
他怎么了
What happened to him?
我们正在调查
That's what we're trying to find out.
天啊  你是说她也是这样
Oh, god. You mean this is what happ-
谁会这么残忍
Who would do something like this?
我和吉尔·布顿谈了  达茜最好的朋友
I spoke to Jill Button, Darcy's B.F.F.
她说她很熟悉
She said she's pretty familiar
达茜的所有朋友和客户
With all of Darcy's friends and clients,
但是她却从来没见过死者
But she's never seen the vic before.
那个法律公司替一些公司做事儿
The law firm does some corporate stuff,
移民方面的
Some immigration work,
但没有任何
But there's nothing to indicate
与案情有关的线索
Any involvement in something like this.
第一个受害者陷入宗教仪式谋杀后
So our first victim gets killed In a religious ritual,
同一天在一个律师身上
And then history repeats itself
上演了同样的悲剧
With this lawyer the very same day?
有个讽刺律师的玩笑
Oh, there's a lawyer joke there somewhere,
我怎么想不起来了
I just can't think of it.
然后凶手在她家乱翻
And then the killer tosses the woman's apartment
他在找什么呢
Looking for what
钱  毒品  还是什么别的呢
Money, drugs, what?
目前了解的情况  达茜是清白的
As far as we can tell, Darcy was clean.
找到了点第一个受害者的线索
Yo, we got a hit on the first victim's prints.
-移民归化局的资料  -贾马尔·伯奥斯
- I.N.S. Database. - Jamal Buonsi?
尼日利亚人
Nigerian national.
18个月前以留学生身份来到美国
Entered the U.S. on a student visa 18 months ago.
是纽约大学的交换生
Was enrolled at N.Y.U. as an exchange student.
-他的签证过期一年了  -对
- His visa expired a year ago. - Yep.
-看来他打算定居  -祝他好运
- Looks like he decided to stay. - Lucky him.
他最后的住址是哪里
Any word on his last known whereabouts?
我查过那户的人家
Yeah, I was able to track down the family
他在学生时代曾和他们住在一起
That he lived with when he was a student.
他们最后一次见到他时
Last time they saw him,
他在去肯尼迪机场的出租车上
He was in a cab on his way to Kennedy.
我想这并不是故事的结局
I take it that's not the end of the story.
还有贾马尔和那家13岁的儿子
Turns out that Jamal and their 13-year-old son
关系不错
Were pretty close.
几个月前  他的父母发现了
Couple of months ago, the folks discovered
他们还有联系  贾马尔的手机号
That they were still in touch. Jamal's cell phone number,
手机帐单的地址  东三街
Billed to an address on East 3rd.
离尸体被发现的地方
That's just a few blocks from
没有几个街区
Where Jamal's body was found.
离达茜·曹的公司也很近
East 3rd's right near Darcy Cho's law firm.
你刚才说达茜·曹的公司
And you said Darcy Cho's firm
是做移民方面业务的
Did some work on immigration.
你和埃斯波西托去那看看
You and Esposito take a ride down there.
拿到达茜·曹的客户名单
I want you to look at Darcy Cho's client list.
看贾马尔是否用了别的名字
Maybe Jamal was using another name.
我们带着搜查令去这儿
We'll get a warrant for the billing address.
找出他到底在找什么
Find out what this guy wants
不要让这个疯子再下手
Before this son of a bitch kills again, all right?
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
我也没期待这楼有门卫看守
I wasn't expecting a doorman building,
六层  没有电梯
But a 6-story walk-up?
你应该体验一下我的第一套房子
You should've seen my first apartment.
餐馆的通风管道
Three flights up on an air shaft
对着三截楼梯
Over a restaurant.
到处都是鸡翅的味道
The whole place smelled like chicken wings.
他们到这儿来  开始新的生活
They come here looking for a new start,
然而他们就住在这儿
And this is what they get...
贫民窟
Slum housing?
只要他们没走就好
Still, for some, it's better than what they left.
听起来贾马尔不是自己住
Sounds like Jamal didn't live alone.
找谁
Yes?
纽约警察局  贝克特探长
Detective Beckett, NYPD.
不
No!
举起手来
Hands! Show me your hands!
移民局的
Immigration.
我不是移民局的  各位  放轻松
I'm not immigration. Everybody, just relax, okay?
你不是移民局的
If you're not from immigration...
-那你是谁  -我是负责凶案的探长
- Then who are you? - I'm a homicide detective.
我来了解贾马尔·伯奥斯的消息
I'm looking for information on Jamal Buonsi.
我们不认识什么贾马尔
We don't know any Jamal.
那你告诉我  为什么在他的电话单上
Then you wanna tell me why his cell phone
注明这里的地址
Is billed to this address?
探长
Detective.
一样的红色法兰绒
Same red flannel.
那是什么
What is it?
那是谁的床
Whose bed is that?
你的红色法兰绒与两起谋杀案有关
We can link the red flannel to two other murders.
在这个国家  这样你会有许多麻烦
In this country, that puts you in a lot of trouble.
-我没有做错任何事  -已经死了两个人了
- I’ve done nothing wrong. - Two people are dead.
其中  男死者和你住在一起
One of them is a man that you lived with.
同样的红色法兰绒  同样的蜡烛  还有她
Same red flannel, same candles. And again, here.
你为什么杀死她  阿齐兹
Why did you kill her, Azi?
我不认识这女的  我从来都没杀过人
I don't know this woman. I haven't killed anyone.
你是告诉我这仅仅是一个巧合
So you're telling me that it's all just a coincidence
这些东西可是在你的屋里
That these things were found in your apartment
你的床底找到的
Under your bed?
这不是我的东西
They weren't mine!
是别人的
They were for someone else.
谁的  你想回尼日利亚吗
Who? Do you want to go back to Nigeria?
这对我来说可就是一个电话的事儿
Because I can arrange that with a single phone call.
他也可以
So can he.
谁
Who?
贾马尔是你的朋友  对不对
Jamal was your friend, wasn't he?
对
Yes.
你难道不想让我们找到凶手吗
Then don't you want us to catch who killed him?
你就不想伸张正义吗
Don't you want justice?
他叫查尔斯
His name is Charles.
-查尔斯·奥尼  -查尔斯·奥尼
- Charles Oni. - Charles Oni.
移民们都知道这个人
Immigrants know this man.
他是我们的房东
He owns the places where we live.
也是我们的老板
He owns the places where we work.
那么贾马尔呢  他也给他打工吗
And what about Jamal? Did he work for him, too?
在运河街上的小店里
At his store on Canal street.
不过那是  那是临时的
But it-it-it-it was only temporary.
那时他在存钱
He was going to save his money to-
准备申请签证  拿到合法的身份
To apply for a visa, become legal.
这和奥尼有什么关系吗
And Oni had a problem with that?
没有
No.
昨天  奥尼来找贾马尔时
Yesterday, when Oni came looking for Jamal,
他说贾马尔偷了他的东西
He said Jamal had taken something.
其实贾马尔并没有偷东西
But Jamal was not a thief.
但是  奥尼固执己见
But Oni insisted.
他说他知道我父亲
He say he knew my father
是我们村里的牧师
Was the priest of our village.
他让我告诉他  如何请神
So he made me to show him how to invoke the spirits.
贾马尔拿了他什么东西
What did Jamal take?
奥尼没说
Oni didn't say.
你怎么不问问呢
Why didn't you ask?
我被吓坏了
'Cause I was scared.
他会杀了我的
Because he would've killed me.
我和你们说这些只不过因为
The only reason I am telling you this now
贾马尔是我的哥们儿
Is because Jamal was a friend.
他不应该就这么死了
He did not deserve to die like that.
奥尼是不可饶恕的
Oni was wrong.
档案中心并没有找到
City records show no vendor's license
查尔斯·奥尼在运河街上的营业记录
For a Charles Oni on Canal street.
显然是违法经营
Well, the guy's exploiting illegals.
我怀疑他用的根本不是真名
I doubt he's gonna use his real name.
肯定不是
Clearly not.
那房子的房东是罗伯特·贝纳特
The apartment is owned by a Robert Burnett.
全市都查不到记录
No listing in the tri-state area,
而且他的邮箱地址在新泽西
And the address is a P.O. Box in Jersey.
那家法律公司的线索断了
Yo, yo, law firm's a dead end.
他们从没听说过叫贾马尔·伯奥斯的
They've never heard of anyone named Jamal Buonsi,
从达茜的客户名单上也找不出任何疑点
And there was nothing suspicious in Darcy's client list.
太棒了
That's perfect,
因为嫌犯也从没听过达茜·曹
'Cause our suspect's never heard of Darcy Cho.
我们还是不知道
We still have no idea what our two victims
这两个受害人有何联系
What our two victims have in common.
-抱歉  女士  -我不要在楼下等
- Excuse me, ma'am. - No, I’m not gonna wait downstairs.
你知不知道你的薪水是谁发的
Do you have any idea who pays your salary?
我可是纳税人
Me and my taxes.
-那是  -没错
- Is that - Uh, yep.
理查德  我在这儿
Richard! Over here!
-煎熬并快乐着  -应该是
- Deep-fried twinkie? - Afraid so.
梅瑞狄斯  好惊喜啊
Meredith! What a surprise.
在洛杉矶  可没人会串门儿
In L.A., no one ever just stops by.
谁能不爱上这里啊
Don't you just love this town?
越来越爱了
More and more by the minute.
梅瑞狄斯  莱恩警官  埃斯波西托警官
Uh, Meredith, these are detectives Ryan, Esposito
还有贝克特探长
And detective Beckett.
贝克特  你的新灵感
Oh, Beckett your new muse.
阿丽克西斯把什么都告诉我了
Alexis told me all about it,
所以我就简单来探个班
And I simply had to stop by.
要知道  我也曾是他的创作灵感
You know, I was his inspiration once.
是啊
Were you now?
现在还经常是呢  对不对  小猫仔
Still am, from time to time. Right, kitten?
小猫仔
Kitten?
我梦见过这样的场景
I had this dream once,
不过梦里我是裸体  也没这么丢人
Only I was naked and far less embarrassed.
反正我们就在附近
Anyway, we were in the neighborhood
正好今晚约了人吃晚餐  所以我想
And I have a dinner tonight, so I thought I would
来这儿把阿丽克西斯交给你
Drop Alexis here instead of
而不是带着她去市中心
Schlepping all the way downtown.
-那不是莎杰帕的包吗  -莎杰帕
- Is that S.J.P.'S purse? - S.J.P.?
莎拉·杰西卡·帕克(欲望都市女主之一)
Sarah Jessica Parker.
在米兰的阿玛尼时装秀上  她用过一次
She wore one just like it to the Armani show in Milan.
《每日独家时尚》上周有介绍
It was on 'fashion scoop daily' last week.
其实这个包是一个受害者的
Well, actually, this purse belongs to one of our victims.
天啊  这太悲惨了
Oh, that is so tragic.
如果这是正品  那就更悲惨了
More tragic, of course, if it'd been the real thing.
-但这并非正品  -这是假货吗
- But... Still. - What, are you saying this was fake?
看它的皮质和做工
Well, look at the leather and the stitching.
这绝对是冒牌货  还不错
It's totally a knockoff. I mean, it's good enough
但也就能骗骗不识货的人
To fool the untrained shopper,
-但绝对骗不到我  -运河街
- But I have a retail eye. - Canal Street.
那里都是卖冒牌手表  行李箱什么的
Canal's where they sell the knockoffs-watches, luggage.
-还有手提包  -达茜办公室里那很近
- And handbags. - Darcy's office is right near Canal.
如果她要买什么冒牌货的话
If she was gonna buy a designer knockoff...
她有可能会去贾马尔那儿
She might've got it from the stall where Jamal works.
奥尼的店里  这就是两个受害者的联系
Oni's stall. That's what connects our two victims.
根据阿齐兹的话做嫌犯画像
Get a sketch from Azi.
也许其他的商贩
Maybe one of the other vendors
-可以认出奥尼来  -是的  长官
- Will be able to I.D. Oni's stall. - You got it, boss.
看见了吗  我就是你的幸运符
See? I always was your lucky charm.
想起来这些  我就舍不得回去
Just think of the things we'll do once I move back.
这就是奥尼  就是他
That's Oni. That's Oni
查尔斯·奥尼
Charles Oni.
现在画像也有了
Now we have a face to go with the name.
运河街会有人认识他的
Someone on Canal Street's gotta know this guy.
卡塞尔去哪儿了
Where's Castle?
回家了
He went home.
因为那个煎熬并快乐着
Deep-fried twinkie, huh?
我问这干什么
I didn't ask.
你为什么不弄一个白板呢
Why don't you get a corkboard
像个正常人一样
Like a normal person?
你为什么不像正常人那样敲门呢
Why don't you knock like a normal person?
你知道吗  今天梅瑞狄斯
You know Meredith
在学校绑架了阿丽克西斯
Kidnapped Alexis from school today?
我们支付了巨额赎金
And we all paid a hefty ransom.
耸人听闻
It's outrageous.
还记得  你巡回表演
You remember your touring production
《歌舞线上》那出剧吗
Of "A Chorus Line"?
害得我在五年级差点留级
I almost had to repeat fifth grade.
那可不一样
Oh, that was different.
我当时既要工作  又要尽好母亲之职
I was working and trying to be a mother.
没有装成女主角  在城里漫无目的闲逛
I wasn't just waltzing into town like a diva,
搅得所有人不得安宁
Disrupting everybody's life.
你很清楚  她就是那种人
That's who she is. You know that.
有没有想过  如果让梅瑞狄斯回到纽约
Have you considered what it's going to be like
生活会变成什么样子
Having Meredith back in New York,
你会受到什么影响
How it's going to affect you?
你是说自己会受到什么影响吧
You mean how it's going to affect you.
应该是我们大家
All of us, actually.
妈妈  你让我怎么办呢
Well, what do you want me to do, mother?
我不可能禁止她搬回纽约
It's not like I could ban her from New York.
有关剧院的整件事  简直是无稽之谈
And this whole theater thing- It's ridiculous.
她已经好几个月没接到角色
You know she hasn't landed a role in months?
是的  我确实打了几个电话
That's right. I made a couple of calls.
你有没有想过  她为什么搬回纽约
Why do you think she's moving back to New York?
她在洛杉矶根本站不住脚
She can't get arrested in LA.
她也不一定能在纽约站住脚
I wonder if she could get arrested in New York.
我知道现在的人
I know people now.
她是不是真的以为
And does she honestly think that she's just gonna
在《听吉姆说》里
Show up with a reel of, what,
客串个小角色
"According to Jim" guest spots,
就能挤掉那些真正的演员
And push some real actor aside,
那些
Some actor who has...
把自己的一生
Who has dedicated their entire life
献给世上最伟大事业的演员吗
To the greatest profession in the world?
不是你选择了戏剧
You don't choose the theater.
而是戏剧选择你
The theater chooses you.
你当初为什么要娶她呢
Why did you marry her, anyway?
我不知道  妈妈  也许她让我想起了你
I don't know, mother. Maybe she reminded me of you.
瞧瞧这些破烂
Look at this crap.
当这么多年的警察  我还是不明白
All my years on the force, I never understood
为什么不把这些取缔
Why we never shut these guys down.
过来
Come here.
瞧  看着好像是古奇的包
See, this is supposed to be a Gucci.
可如果仔细看
But if you look close,
这上面的首字母是CC  而不是GG
Instead of the "G.G.," the initials say "C.C."
我看不出来  老兄  做得很像
I don't know. That's pretty close, bro.
只要有差别  这些家伙就不会被抄
But not exact. And that's what keeps these guys
从技术层面上讲
From getting busted. See, technically,
这不算是对名牌的仿冒  而是致敬
It's not an imitation. It's a homage.
致敬  说得好
A "homage." Right.
两位女士
You ladies picking out something
选好商品了吗
Pretty for yourselves?
-带搜查证了吗  -哪一间
- You got the warrant?  - Which one is it?
这里已经被翻得乱七八糟
This place has been trashed.
伙计们  同样的香奈尔包包
You guys, same Chanel bags.
很奇怪  跟受害人的皮包一样都被剪烂了
That's weird-Shredded, like our victim's purse.
也许达茜当时不是用皮包自卫的
Maybe Darcy wasn't using it to defend herself.
这个有所不同
This one looks different.
和我们在受害人嘴里发现的
It doesn't look like the ones that we found
不太一样
In the other victims' mouths.
我以前见过这种标志
I've seen this symbol before.
这是死亡的标志
That's the symbol for death.
那家伙为什么在自己的店里
Why would a guy mark his own stall
画个死亡的标志
With the death symbol?
不是他画的
He wouldn't.
这标志是送给他的
The symbol was meant for him.
查尔斯·奥尼被人画上了死亡记号
Charles Oni's been marked for death.
内衬都被剪开了
The linings have all been cut out.
-这些都是进口来的  对吧  -是的
- All of this stuff is imported, right?  - Yeah.
要知道  冒牌货是
You know, knockoffs would be
走私贩子的最佳运输渠道
The perfect delivery system for a smuggler.
他们走私什么呢
Yeah, but what are they smuggling?
那个被画上死亡记号的家伙
The only person who can tell us that
是唯一能回答问题的人
Has been marked for death.
如果他尚在人间
Well, if he is still alive,
应该不会留在本地
He doesn't have any incentive to stick around.
卡塞尔
Castle?
他要去哪里
Where's he going?
通知出入境处
Notify passport control.
把奥尼的画像传给他们
Get 'em the sketch of Oni and tell 'em
让他们把他的名字或化名  都列入禁飞名单
To put his name and aliases on the no-fly list.
明白  头儿
You got it, boss.
卡塞尔
Castle?
-卡塞尔  -我上电视了
- Castle!  - I'm on TV.
你神经失常吗
Are you having a breakdown?
没有  只是有重大突破
Not a breakdown. A breakthrough.
我真是英俊得要命  是吧
And I really am ruggedly handsome, am I?
快说你的重大突破
I'm waiting for the breakthrough.
看看身后  如果那台摄像机一直开着
Look behind me. If that camera's recording...
我们就能知道是谁砸了店面
Then we'd be able to see who trashed the stall.
我能说什么呢
What can I say?
人们在摄像机前干的那些事
I mean, you would not believe
说了可能你都不信
The things people do in front of a camera.
洗耳恭听
I'm listening.
有个小妞正好站在
Like, this one chick, she's standing there
那家店的前面
Right in front of the store,
接着  开始脱她的
And she starts to take off her, uh-
你只要把前几天的录像
Just show us the recordings
给我们就可以  听见了吗
From the past couple of days, okay?
血糖降低
Her blood sugar gets low,
她就会暴躁起来
She gets a little cranky.
闭嘴  小猫仔
Zip it... kitten.
很抱歉  我给不了你们录像
I'm sorry, but I can't show you the recording.
还要搜查证吗
You need a warrant?
没用  已经卖了
Wouldn't help. Sold it.
橱窗里的摄像机卖了吗
Sold the camera in the window?
昨天有个人进来
Some guy rolls in here yesterday,
非要那台不可
Asked for that one specifically.
我说还有别的摄像机  带包装的
I told him we got others, ones with boxes.
但是  他只要橱窗里那台
But he wants the one in the window.
他长什么样子
What does he look like?
6英尺高  大块头  黑人有口音
6', big, black, had an accent.
是他吗
Was it him?
不是他  这人是街对面的店主
No, he owns the stall across the street.
你们认识吗
You know him?
打过招呼  但这家伙看起来  很有分量
We say hi. But this guy- He seemed, uh, heavy.
不是说身体上的
Not in the physical sense-
他有那么股劲儿  明白吗
Just something about him, you know?
一看就像干过什么  坏事之类的
Like he'd seen things, bad things.
还有什么
What else?
他付的现金
He paid cash-retail.
我要多少  给多少
I mean, at my prices?
甚至都没有还价
He didn't even try to negotiate once.
你是否愿意跟警方合作
Would you be willing to
做一张他的画像
Work with a police sketch artist?
真人照片不是更好吗
Wouldn't a real picture be better?
你不是说
You said that
他把摄像机和录像带都带走了
He took the camera and the recordings.
女士  这可是电子产品商店
Lady, this is an electronics store.
这里到处都是摄像机
I got cameras all over this place.
对对  他像那种
Yeah, he does look like the kind of guy
在你家地板上画死亡记号的人
Who'd paint a death symbol on your floor.
让我不明白的是
What I don't get is,
他要那台摄像机干什么呢
Why would he want the camera?
和我们目的一样
'Cause he had the same idea we did.
我们要那台机子
We wanted the camera
是想找到他
Because we wanted to find him.
那他在找什么呢
Well, what was he looking for?
还有  包里到底有什么
And what was inside the purses?
埃斯波西托  是我  真的
Esposito. Yeah. Really?
什么时候  不不  完全可以
When? No, no, no. Absolutely.
把他带来
Bring him in.
运输安全管理局刚刚用我们的画像
T.S.A. just pulled Charles Oni out of
在肯尼迪机场的安检处抓到查尔斯·奥尼
The security line at J.F.K. Off our sketch.
-老兄  干得漂亮  -多谢
- Good call, bro.  - Thank you.
他准备去哪里
Where was he going?
尼日利亚  用假名罗伯特·贝纳特
Nigeria. Under the name Robert Burnett.
我不懂你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我准备回家探亲
I was going home to visit my family.
为什么只买单程票
Then why'd you only have a one-Way ticket?
我母亲病了
My mother is ill.
不知道什么时候能回来
I did not know when I'd be returning.
能够去探望自己的母亲  多幸福
Must be nice, being able to see your mother,
可是贾马尔·伯奥斯
Something that Jamal Buonsi
永远没机会回家探亲了
Will never get a chance to do.
我们掌握到
We know that you are involved
你与这两起凶杀案都有关系
In both of these murders.
阿齐兹  那个受你威逼去寻找贾马尔的人
Azi- the man that you intimidated into finding Jamal
迫切地希望指证你
He is very eager to testify against you.
很显然  他对自己的信仰
Apparently, he takes his religious beliefs
非常虔诚
Very seriously.
他可不相信
Doesn't believe Voodoo
伏都教是用来杀人的工具
Should be used to kill people.
我没杀人
I didn't kill anyone.
那为什么要找贾马尔
Then why were you looking for Jamal?
告诉我  包里有什么
Tell me something- What's in the purse?
奥尼先生  你在走私什么
What are you smuggling, Mr. Oni?
我需要律师
I want a lawyer.
想清楚了吗  一旦把律师叫来
Are you sure? Because if you get a lawyer,
你一小时后就得离开这里
You'll be out of here in about an hour,
我不会让你出城
And I won't let you leave town,
可是你却很想
And that's exactly what you want, isn't it,
离开这儿  对吗
To leave town?
奥尼先生  许多人怕你
You scare a lot of people, Mr. Oni-
非法移民  做非法勾当的
Immigrants, illegals.
说说看
Tell me...
谁让你这么害怕
Who scares you?
我不认识这个人
I don't know this man.
可他认识你
He knows you.
事实上  他给你注上了死亡标志
Matter of fact, he's marked you for death.
贾马尔为你干活  他死了
Jamal worked for you, and he's dead.
达茜·曹只是从你那里买了个包
Darcy Cho-She just bought a purse from you,
现在也死了
And now she's dead.
为什么
Why?
除非有人保护我  否则我不说
I won't talk without protection.
你不告诉我是谁
I can't protect you
我没办法保护你
Unless you tell me from what.
他叫穆克塔·贝勒
His name is Mukhtar Baylor.
很凶残  很危险
Very bad, very dangerous.
当过童子军
Former child soldier.
他们称他  贝宁的刽子手
They call him "the butcher of Benin."
他在美国做什么
What's he doing in the U.S.?
贩卖毒品  贩卖妇女
He traffics-Drugs, women,
什么赚钱干什么
Whatever will make him money.
是他杀了贾马尔和那女人
It is him that killed Jamal and the woman.
为什么
Why?
如果我说了  你们会不会保护我
If I tell you, you will protect me?
奥尼是个制假贩子
Oni's a counterfeiter.
为不法份子做假证件
He gets papers for illegals-
假护照  假签证  一应俱全
Passports, visas, whatever they need.
是那个圈子里的贵人
A real friend to the community.
奥尼为贝勒的偷渡客
Oni also provided Baylor with documents
提供伪造的证件
For his traffickers.
缝进皮包的内衬里面
Sewn inside the lining of his purses.
是的  他把这些包放在店铺的后面
Yeah, which he keeps in the back of the stall.
千算万算  没算到《每日独家时尚》
Only he didn't count on "Fashion Scoop Daily."
网站吧
The web site.
是的  有篇莎拉·杰西卡·帕克的文章
Yeah, the article on Sarah Jessica Parker?
让这种皮包走俏
Appears there was a run on the purses.
是的  第一个受害人  贾马尔
Yeah. Our first vic, Jamal-
卖光了摆在前面的货
He sold bags out front.
他不知道奥尼的花招
He didn't know about Oni's scam.
前面的货卖光了
When he ran out of bags,
就把后面的货拿出来卖
He sold the ones from the back.
为什么不让奥尼再做些假证件
Why didn't he just get Oni to forge more documents?
那要花时间  贝勒没时间了
It takes time, and Baylor doesn't have time.
证件是给他非洲的哥哥用的
The papers are for Baylor’s brother in Africa.
因为贩毒  尼日利亚警方
The Nigerian officials are closing in on him
马上要缉捕他
For drug trafficking.
如果贝勒不抓紧时间把他弄到美国来
If Baylor doesn't get him to the U.S. soon.
他就会被处死
They'll execute him.
据奥尼供述
Oni says Baylor operates
贝勒在市中心有个仓库
Out of a warehouse downtown.
把这个恶棍揪出来
Find this dirtball
不要再有人受害  听到吗
Before the murders someone else, all right?
这个包是谁的
Where did the bag come from?
不好意思  是我的
Oh, sorry, that's mine.
为了以防万一
I felt, given everything that's happened,
我要有所准备
I should be prepared.
我特别订制来的
I got this special order.
看这个
And look.
-作家  -帅吧
- "Writer"?  - Cool, huh?
一点也不帅
No, not cool.
你不需要防弹衣
You don't need a vest.
如果你打中我  难道不会流血吗
If you shoot me, do I not bleed?
你不会中枪  知道为什么吗
You're not gonna get shot. And you know why?
因为你不用亲临战场
Because you are going nowhere near the gunfire.
你要留在这里
You're staying here.
我们都清楚那会怎么样
We've seen how well that works.
卡塞尔  老实待在这里  什么也别做
Stay here, Castle, and don't do anything.
这是我们要抓的人  认好了吗
All right, this is our guy. Got him?
行动
Let's go.
爸爸  爸爸  爸爸
Dad! Dad! Dad!
Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad!
爸爸  爸爸  爸爸
Dad! Dad! Dad!
Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad!
911  请尽快回电  阿丽克西斯
911! Call home ASAP Alexis
我得接个电话
I'm gonna- I'm gonna just get that.
-阿丽克西斯  出什么事啦  -理查德  知道吗
- Alexis? What's wrong?  - Richard, guess what.
-梅瑞狄斯  -我看上个地方
- Meredith?  - I found a place.
完美至极  宽敞  明亮
A perfect place. It's light, spacious
只要106万
And only a million six.
短信发送人显示是  阿丽克西斯
But the text said "Alexis."
还说是紧急事件
It said it was an emergency.
是啊  不然你怎么会回我电话
Well, how else was I gonna get you to call me back?
但是  你不是在阁楼吗
B- but- are you at the loft?
我刚好在附近  突然想去厕所
Mm, I was in the neighborhood and I had to pee,
所以我让爱德华多放我进来
So I had Eduardo let me in.
然后打给房地产公司
So I called the realtor,
事情是这样的  我需要你帮我做担保
And here's the thing- I may need you to cosign the loan.
梅瑞狄斯  我们离婚了
Meredith, we're divorced.
我是不会帮你担保的
I- I'm not gonna cosign a loan for you.
这也是为了阿丽克西斯
It's for Alexis, too.
我是说  这儿只有一间卧室
I mean, it's only a one- bedroom,
你也希望她来时能住的舒服些
But you want her to be comfortable when she visits, right?
听着  我再打给你  我正忙着呢
Look, can I call you back? I'm right in the middle
忙着抓一名极度危险的尼日利亚毒贩
Of capturing a very dangerous Nigerian drug lord...
这可是件大事
It's kind of a thing.
好吧  那一会儿再说  理查德
Okay, later then. Hey, Richard?
怎么了
Yeah.
谢谢你
Thanks.
-谢什么  -容忍我
- For what?  - Putting up with me.
我一直麻烦你  但是
I know I’ve been a handful, but...
一旦安定下来  一切会好起来的
Once things settle down, I think it's gonna be great.
就是那个人  就是他
That's the guy. That's the guy!
那个
Hey! The-
你在听我讲话吗
Are you even listening to me?
这下我闯大祸了
This is gonna bite me in the ass.
卡塞尔
Castle!
什么叫没记住车牌号码
What do you mean you didn't get the plate?
是这样的  那辆车
Uh, there was a- it was coming
是什么车
What kind of car was it?
-挺大的  我猜是越野车  -你猜的
- Uh, it was big. It was an S.U.V., I think  -You think?
-什么颜色的  -黑色或是深蓝色
- What about the color? - Um, black. Uh, dark blue.
做目击证人太难了
Uh, it's- it's very hard being a witness.
我不明白你们怎么会相信
I don't know how you guys ever get a conviction.
我通常很注意细节
I'm usually really good with the detailed stuff.
我只是分心了
I just- I got distracted.
你在出任务的时候忙着接电话
Yeah, you were rolling calls during a tac strike.
-有意思  -大家都以为他在里面
- Interesting. - He was supposed to be inside the building!
你衬衣是什么颜色的
What about the color of your shirt?
现在是什么颜色  黑色还是蓝色
What is that right now? Is that black or blue?
我看不清  阳光太刺眼了
I-I-I couldn't quite tell. The sun was in my eyes.
太诡异了
Weird.
真的太诡异了
Really weird.
同样的红色法兰绒
It's the same red flannel.
这个伏都教徒还是个瑜珈狂人
Hey... vodun guy's a yoga nut.
谁说冷血杀手
Well, just 'cause you're a cold-blooded killer
就不知道如何照顾自己
Doesn't mean you don't take care of yourself.
你们看
You guys.
是那家电子商店的摄像机
The camera from the electronics store.
是吧  也不是毫无收获啊
See? Not a complete bust.
那是贾马尔
There's Jamal.
还有达茜·曹
And Darcy Cho.
倒回去  倒回去  好了
Go back, go back, go back, go back. Okay.
再退  再退  好的
More. More. All right.
停  看来除了达茜还有其他人
Stop. Well, looks like someone else besides Darcy
从贾马尔那儿买了香奈儿的包
Bought a Chanel bag from Jamal.
她还拿着瑜伽垫
And she's carrying a yoga mat.
所以他就买了这个录像机
That's why he bought the camera.
贝勒在找她  他想要他的护照
Baylor's looking for her. He wants his passport
他在找买了那种包的人
So he's hunting down everyone that bought that purse.
纽约人口有八百万
Eight million people in the city.
他没法儿找到她的
He'll never find her.
他能找到达茜·曹  也能找到她
He found Darcy Cho. He'll find her.
除非我们先找到她
Not if we find her first.
放大她的手部
You zoom in on her hand.
她拿着一杯爪哇咖啡
She's got a coffee from Java Loft.
-所以 -所以我们要在运河街上
- So? - So we're looking for a yoga studio
找爪哇咖啡店附近的瑜伽会所
Near a java loft somewhere off canal street.
范围太大  而且贝勒已经先我们一步
Gotta be a dozen possibilities.  Baylor's got a head start.
是的  但我现在有个超棒的计划
Yes, but I’ve got an awesome service plan now.
我们找的是练习瑜伽的女孩儿
We're looking for yoga girl.
你们去查查是否还有人买了那个包
You guys see if anyone else bought that purse.
运河街附近的五个街区  有四家爪哇咖啡店
There are four java lofts within five blocks of canal street.
有瑜珈会所吗
And yoga studios?
录像上显示时间是三点二十二分
The time stamp on the video was 3:22.
我们要找的是附近的瑜珈会所
We're looking for a yoga studio nearby
而且是三点下课的
With a class that ends at about 3:00.
也许她在上课的路上呢
Maybe the woman was on her way to yoga class.
你喝完咖啡
You ever try doing a half moon pose
还能做出半月式吗
Cranked up on caffeine?
你会都吐出来的
It completely throws off your chi.
相信我  她是下课后买的咖啡
Trust me, she bought her coffee after class.
三点下课
A class finishing around 3:00 p.m.
所以她有充足的时间买咖啡
Would give her enough time to buy a coffee.
但在出运河街前还没有喝完
But enough time to finish it before canal street.
明白
Got it.
纽约警局  你认识这个女孩吗
NYPD. Do you know this girl?
戴安娜·爱德华  她到底犯了什么事儿
Diana Edwards. What's she done?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你找她的第二个警察了
You're the second cop that's come in looking for her.
还来过一个警察
Another cop was here?
是  他几分钟前刚刚离开
Yeah, he just left a few minutes ago.
是贝勒  马上给我们黛安娜的住址
Baylor. We need Diana's address right now.
戴安娜·爱德华  纽约警局  快开门
Diana Edwards! NYPD! Open up!
我能把门踹开吗
Can I kick it down?
不行  小猫仔
Sorry, kitten.
纽约警局
NYPD!
知道了 好的  放松点
Okay, okay! Take it easy!
贝克特探长  你是戴安娜·爱德华吗
Detective Beckett, NYPD. Are you Diana Edwards?
你还好吗
Is everything okay?
很好啊
Fine.
有录像显示
We have a video surveillance
两天前你在运河街
Of you purchasing a Chanel bag
买了一个香奈儿的包
On Canal street two days ago.
我知道你们在查假货
Wow, I know you guys are cracking down on the knockoffs,
但是我
But I...
-包在哪儿  -那边
- Where's the bag?  - Over there.
抱歉  你这是在干什么
Excuse me! Hey! What are you doing that for?
怎么回事
What's going on?
你太走运了
You are a very lucky lady.
我不明白  我惹麻烦了吗
I don't understand. Am I in trouble?
没有  但从现在起  只买正品
No. But from now on, always buy retail.
我是贝克特探长
Detective Beckett.
91大街和百老汇街交接处  要求支援
I need a unit at 91st and Broadway
快报警!
Call 9-1-1!
-把护照给我  -马上放下武器
- Give me the passport! - Put down your weapon, now!
护照给我
Give me the passport!
贝勒  从现在起
Baylor, any minute now,
这里随时会被警察包围
This place is gonna be crawling with cops!
不要把事情搞得更糟
Don't make things worse than they are!
把我要的给我  我就走
Give me what I want, and I walk away!
这种场景我写过一百多次了
I've written this scene about a hundred times.
我们要是把东西给他  你知道会怎么样吗
We give him what he wants, you know how it ends?
很糟糕  很糟糕等于我们死定了
Badly. And by "badly," I mean us dead.
-趴下  -你趴下
- Just stay down. - You stay down.
从这儿我没法儿打中他
I can't shoot him from down here.
他也不能
Yeah, he can't shoot you, either.
-我看不到他  -他在移动
- I can't see him. - He's moving.
我只剩两发子弹了
I've only got two rounds left.
我得干脆点  先要设法看见他
I need a clean shot. I gotta get eyes on him somehow.
你拿手机做什么
What's with you and phones?
我不是说着玩
I'm not playing games!
在这儿我找不到角度开枪
I don't have an angle on him from down here.
-我要杀了你们两个 -这样吧
- I will kill you both! - Okay.
我们开枪  他也会  但他就暴露了
When we shoot, he shoots. He'll be exposed.
我做诱饵  你对付他
I'll set the pick, you take him down.
用什么做诱饵
Set the pick with what?
这个  你会有危险的
This. You're gonna get yourself shot.
-除非你打中他  -卡塞尔
- Not if you make your shot count. - Castle!
快准备好
Just be ready.
这是最后的警告
This is your last warning!
现在
Now!
这真值得干一杯
I'd say this deserves a toast.
贝勒会没事的
Baylor's gonna make it.
你没事吧  卡塞尔
You okay, Castle?
我的第一次枪战
My first gun battle.
也是你的最后一次
Your last gun battle.
别那么悲观嘛
Don't be so pessimistic.
我觉得我做的不错
I think I handled myself pretty well.
是  你算是救了我一命
Yeah. You probably saved my life.
算是  根本就是我救了你
Probably? I definitely saved your life.
你应该明白  这意味着什么吧
And you know what that means, don't you?
-意味着你欠我的  -欠你什么
- It means you owe me. - Owe you what?
无论我要什么都行
Whatever I want.
而且你很了解我要什么  对不对
And you know exactly what I want, don't you?
知道我真的很想要你做什么吗
You know what I really, really want you to do?
永远  永远  别叫我小猫仔
Never... Ever... Call me "kitten."
-爸爸   -什么事
- Dad? - Yeah, sweetie?
理论上  有可能你爱一个人
Hypothetically, is it okay to love someone
但不愿意总在一起吗
But not want them around all the time?
-说的是你妈妈  -我爱她  真的
- You mean mom? - I love her. I do.
我知道  而且很高兴你爱她
I know you do, and I’m glad you do.
可是  爸爸  她快把我逼疯了
But, dad, she drives me crazy.
妈妈们就是这样
Yeah. That's what moms do.
但如果她要是留在纽约
But if she lives here...
理查德  理查德  阿丽克西斯
Richard? Richard. Alexis.
我会帮你保守秘密的
Your secret's safe with me.
到底有没有人在家啊
Hello? Anyone home? Hello?
你们肯定无法相信
You will not believe what happened.
经纪人给我来电话了
I got a call from my agent.
我受邀主演一部独立制作电影
I've been offered a huge role in a new indie film.
妈妈  真是太好了
Mom, that's awesome.
是的  但也有个坏消息  亲爱的
It is. But... Here's the bad news, sweetie.
回纽约的计划
I'm gonna have to put my plans to move back
要压后了
To New York on hold.
这让我们怎么办啊
Oh... How ever will we manage?
没关系的  妈妈
Well, that's okay, mom.
-听起来是个好机会   -绝对是
- It sounds like a huge opportunity. - It is. It really is.
而且  百老汇永远在这儿
Besides, it's not like Broadway's going anywhere.
等我老了再来剧院也不迟
I can always do theater when I’m too old for Hi-Def.
那你什么时候回洛杉矶啊
Uh, so when do you need to be back in L.A.?
明天  现在我得回酒店收拾行李了
Tomorrow. I need to get back to my hotel and pack,
我就是想先告诉你这个好消息
But I wanted to tell you the good news.
还有很多好玩的事情没做
There's so much fun stuff we didn't get to do.
-我保证很快就回来  -我知道
- But I’ll be back soon, I promise. - I know.
我爱你  妈妈
I love you, mom.
-谢谢你带我逛街  -我随时都愿意
- Thanks for taking me shopping. - Oh, anytime.
-再见了  玛莎  -梅瑞狄斯
- Good-bye, Martha. - Meredith.
你知道  我总舍不得送你走
You know I always hate to see you go.
下次  来次前十名的
Next time- top ten.
前十名的
Top ten.
好的  爸爸  坦白吧
Okay, dad, spill.
-什么   -你都做了什么
- What? - What did you do?
什么也没做啊
Nothing.
我的业务经理打电话给我
Oh. My business manager called I
说有一个千载难逢的投资机会
With an excellent investment opportunity
是一部小型  独立制作的文艺电影
A small, artsy independent feature.
真是我的好儿子
Oh, that's my boy!
她真的很适合那个角色
Eh, she's perfect for the role.
我觉得  又可以帮他们
I'm doing them a favor. I think.
希望你不会介意
I hope you don't mind.
养活你已经很辛苦了
Raising one parent's hard enough.
养两个人  我不知道该怎么办了
I don't know what I’d do if I had to raise two.
有没有适合我的角色
There wasn't a little part for me...
-没有  -就是那部文艺
- No, no. - In the artsy...
不是吧
Uh, no.